Royal Capital, Castle Atismata
What?!
What do you mean you can't find the petrified Ragnarok?!
The stonemasons reported
they only found traces of it.
Traces?
Yes.
The report says they found an empty shell.
So where did it go?
They never said there'd be swimming practice.
Will the boy take part as well?
Swimming together? As someone who despises men,
are you really going to allow that?
Celis?
Saniya.
I told Luno, so I should tell you too.
I don't actually despise men.
Truth be told, I look up to
and am fascinated by them.
When I was very young, I had a teacher
who was a strong and kind man.
But I... I don't know how to interact with young men.
Moreover...
In my position, I can't afford to rely on men.
Because I'm the eldest daughter of House Ralgris, one of the Four Great Houses,
and also the captain of the knight squadron.
Fight for the sky
afuredasu kanjou mou tomaranai
I can't stop the overflowing emotions
mune ni idaitai bokura no gensou
The illusions we hold so dear
Just revolution
kienai aza ni obiete ite mo
Fear of the scar that won't disappear
toki ga mujou ni sugiteku dake
Won't stop the ruthless passage of time
susumeyo aru ga mama
Go forth, the way you are
Let's burst up!
ima koso kawaru toki
Now is the time for change
Let's boost up!
kakumei no kane no ne ga
The sound of the bell of revolution
doko made mo hibiite yuku
Resounds far and wide
To be the soldier
mou koko ni wa irarenai
We can't stay here any longer
To be the soldier
kaze wo kitte yuke ikite yuke
Cut through the wind, live your life
hiryuu no gotoku
Like a flying dragon
hajimari ga michiru mama densetsu ni nare
As the beginning draws near, become a legend
tokihanatte yuke tonde yuke
Release yourself, fly ahead
inochi wo tagirasete
Overflow with life
erabareshi mono wo matsu sekai wa owari da New age
The world that waits for a chosen one is over! New age!
m 1135.125 677.5 b 1139.625 676.25 1143.125 675.25 1147.625 674 1147.625 681.5 1147.625 688.5 1147.625 696.5 1150.375 695 1152 693.875 1153.625 693.125 1162.875 689 1169.625 693.125 1170 703.125 1170.25 707.875 1169.875 712.625 1170.25 717.375 1170.375 720.5 1171.5 723.625 1172.25 727.125 1168.5 727.125 1164 727.125 1159.375 727.125 1164.75 718 1162.375 708.375 1161.375 699 1161.25 697.625 1157.625 695.25 1156.5 695.75 1153.5 697 1148.875 699.25 1148.625 701.5 1147.75 709.75 1148.25 718.25 1148.25 727 1145.625 727 1140.875 727 1136 727 1141.875 720.375 1141.75 682.875 1135.125 677.5 m 847.75 690.875 b 846.875 688.5 846.625 686.875 845.625 685.875 843.5 683.125 841.125 678.875 838.5 678.625 835.125 678.25 830.625 680.25 828.125 682.75 820.875 690.375 821 713.25 828.375 720.75 830.75 723.125 835.25 723.75 838.875 724.125 840.125 724.375 843 721.5 843 720 842.875 715.875 841.625 711.875 840.75 707.375 844 707.375 849.125 707.375 853.375 707.375 852.5 711.125 851.875 715.25 850.625 719.375 850.125 721.375 849.125 723.625 847.5 724.75 836.875 732.625 820.375 728.25 816.75 715.625 814.5 708 814.25 699.25 815.75 691.5 817.875 679.625 827.75 673.875 839.75 675 848.75 675.875 851.25 680.25 847.75 690.875 m 749.125 727 b 750.875 723.125 752.75 720 753.75 716.625 757.625 704.75 761 692.75 764.875 680.875 765.625 678.625 767.75 676.875 769.25 675 770.75 677 772.75 678.75 773.625 681 777.75 692.5 781.5 704.125 785.625 715.625 787 719.375 789 722.875 790.875 727 786.125 727 781.125 727 778.125 727 777.125 721.75 777.75 714.625 775 713 771 710.75 764.5 711.5 759.5 712.75 756.375 713.625 756.75 722.875 759.875 727 755.875 727 752.375 727 749.125 727 m 767.125 685.5 b 764.625 694 762.75 700.75 760.625 707.625 765.5 707.625 769.625 707.625 774.375 707.625 772 700.5 769.875 693.875 767.125 685.5 m 1091.25 695.25 b 1094.625 694.25 1098 693.125 1101.625 692 1104.5 703.75 1099.125 716 1105.5 727.625 1101.625 727.375 1097.625 727 1093.5 726.75 1093.625 726.125 1093.75 725.625 1093.75 725 1090.75 726.125 1087.875 727.75 1084.75 728.125 1077.75 729.125 1073.125 725.375 1072.625 718.25 1072.25 713.875 1072.75 709.25 1072.375 704.875 1072.125 701.625 1071.125 698.625 1070.375 694.875 1072.625 694.125 1075.875 693.125 1080.25 691.75 1080.25 699.5 1080.125 706.625 1080.25 713.75 1080.375 718.375 1080 724.375 1086.75 724.125 1092.75 724 1095.125 719.625 1094.625 713.75 1094 707.625 1093.875 701.625 1093.5 695.5 1092.75 695.5 1092 695.375 1091.25 695.25 m 1033.875 688.5 b 1031 682 1027.875 676.5 1019 680.625 1019 693.375 1018.75 706.5 1019.25 719.75 1019.375 722 1022.5 724.125 1024.375 726.625 1018.75 726.625 1012.125 726.625 1004.125 726.625 1012.625 723.625 1010.625 717.125 1010.75 711.375 1010.75 701 1010.75 690.5 1010.75 680.75 1001.625 676.25 998.875 682.625 996.375 689 995.75 688.625 995.25 688.375 994.75 688 995.125 684.375 995.5 680.625 995.875 676.125 1007.75 676.125 1019.25 675.25 1030.5 676.375 1037.5 677.125 1034.25 683.625 1033.875 688.5 m 946.75 719 b 950.125 721.125 953.25 724.125 956.875 725.125 958.875 725.75 963 723.5 963.875 721.5 964.625 719.75 962.625 716 960.75 714.25 958.125 711.875 954 710.875 951.375 708.375 949.125 706.125 946.5 702.25 947 699.75 947.75 696.875 951.375 693.75 954.375 692.625 964.125 689.125 970 692.375 970.125 700.125 966.875 698.25 963.875 695.875 960.25 694.875 958.75 694.375 955.875 696.625 954.625 698.375 954.125 699.125 956.25 702.375 957.75 703.5 961.125 706 965.375 707.5 968.625 710 975.375 715.5 974 724.625 965.625 726.875 960.875 728.25 955.125 728.125 950.25 727 948 726.375 946.75 721.75 945 719 945.625 719 946.25 719 946.75 719 m 925.25 727.375 b 921.25 727.375 916.25 727.375 911.125 727.375 916.75 718.875 916.5 683 910.5 677.5 914.5 676.25 918.125 675.25 922.625 673.875 922.625 688.75 922.5 702.875 922.75 717.125 922.75 720.25 924.25 723.5 925.25 727.375 m 897.75 727.25 b 890.75 727.25 885.625 727.25 880.25 727.25 885 721.125 885.25 701.625 880.25 694.75 884.625 695.75 888.5 688.75 891.5 693.875 896.5 693.5 900.5 692.875 904.5 693.25 905.25 693.375 905.625 697.25 906.125 699.5 904.375 699 902 699.125 901.125 698 897 693.25 893.625 697.375 893.25 699.75 892.25 707.5 892.5 715.5 892.75 723.375 892.75 724.375 895.125 725.25 897.75 727.25 m 1038.625 727 b 1044.125 721.125 1044.25 701.25 1039.625 696.125 1047.875 691.625 1048.25 691.625 1051 695.125 1054.375 693.875 1057.5 692.125 1060.75 692 1062.375 692 1064.25 694.75 1065.625 696.75 1066 697.25 1064.625 699.125 1064 700.375 1062.5 699.375 1060.75 698.625 1059.5 697.375 1055.5 693.5 1052.5 697.625 1052.25 699.75 1051.375 707.5 1051.5 715.5 1051.625 723.375 1051.75 724.375 1054.125 725.25 1056.375 727 1050 727 1044.75 727 1038.625 727 m 1112 693.75 b 1114.5 690.875 1117.75 687.125 1121.625 682.75 1122 685.625 1122.375 688.625 1122.75 692 1125.25 692.5 1128 693 1130.625 693.5 1130.625 693.875 1130.625 694.25 1130.625 694.75 1128.125 695.25 1125.625 695.625 1122.375 696.375 1122.375 704.125 1121.75 712.125 1122.75 719.875 1123.125 722.25 1127.875 724 1131.5 726.75 1128 727 1123.5 728.5 1119.875 727.125 1117.375 726.25 1115.25 721.75 1114.75 718.5 1113.875 713.125 1114.75 707.5 1114.375 702.125 1114.125 699.25 1112.875 696.5 1112 693.75 m 859.5 695.25 b 863.75 694.125 867.25 693.125 870.875 692.125 873.375 703.625 868.625 715.75 874.125 726.875 870.25 726.875 865.25 726.875 860 726.875 865.5 720.25 865.375 701.125 859.5 695.25 m 935.125 692.875 b 934.5 688.375 933.625 683.875 933.375 679.375 933.25 678 935.125 676.5 936.125 675.125 937.125 676.375 939 677.75 939 679.125 938.875 683.75 938 688.375 937.375 693 936.625 693 935.875 693 935.125 692.875 m 860.875 682.625 b 863.625 680.375 865.375 677.875 867 678 868.5 678.125 871.5 681 871.25 682.125 871 684.125 868.875 686.5 866.875 687.125 865.75 687.5 863.625 684.75 860.875 682.625
Hey! Luxy!
Over here!
Come on. Everyone's waiting for you.
M-My bad. I didn't see anything.
No. I think you're misunderstanding something.
Huh?
The clothes we're wearing are not underwear.
Apparently these are called swimsuits.
It's the first time I've worn one though.
Was that cold, Lu?
Phi?
Yeah, it was.
I told you, it's cold!
Philuffy's in high spirits.
Stop it already! Hey, come on! It's cold!
That's unusual.
Yes.
I'm out of here!
Oh, he ran away.
What's wrong, Lisha?
Well, this shows more of my belly than I expected.
It's fine.
And you look great in that swimsuit.
Wh-What are you talking about, you perv?!
What?
Oh, my. How nice.
Boys and girls enjoying their youth.
We came all the way out to this island,
so we should let loose a bit.
Miss Relie too?
Oh, you shouldn't discriminate, Lux.
I'm a girl too, you know.
Yeah, a "girl"...
Airi?
You're the worst, Lux!
What? I didn't say anything!
Even your own sister! You deviant!
What?!
I mean no disrespect, Headmistress,
but we came to this island to train.
You say that, but you still came,
and in a pretty cute swimsuit too.
Th-This is what Luno—I mean,
a younger student chose for me,
because we heard there'd be swimming training.
Speaking of which, where is Luno?
Luno? Did we have a girl by that name?
Lux, we have a small present for you.
Huh?
What?!
There's no need for me to be bait now!
I don't think the suspicious man
from school could possibly be here.
We can't be sure of that.
Yeah.
Yes. The investigation is going well.
Huh?
What are you—
Come on, now!
This again?
When else would we get the chance to see Luxy in a sexy swimsuit?
Yes. You have to supply the demand.
What are you talking about?!
Resign yourself to your fate!
Wha—Stop! Stop!
Celis!
I'm sorry.
Oops.
You'll soon face me in battle,
yet you think you have time to fool around?
No, that's not what—
Oh, my.
Lux...
Let's go, Celis.
Headmistress, if there's no swimming practice, we'll be heading back to the lodging house.
I have to apologize to Lux Arcadia.
What do you mean?
I learned fencing and tactics from Mr. Wade Roadbelt.
Huh?
He was Lux Arcadia's grandfather.
It would be no exaggeration to say
that I owe all my skill to him.
But in the end, Mr. Wade died because of me.
That's why I want to protect his grandson from danger.
That's also one of the reasons why I must win the upcoming duel.
But I can't afford to lose either.
We'll have you two spar.
As a special provision,
the winner's request shall be granted.
Lux Arcadia's request is to remain in our school
and take part in the subjugation of the Ragnarok.
Celistia's request is for Lux Arcadia to leave the school
and be prohibited from taking part in the subjugation.
Are your requests as stated?
Yes.
Well, then, draw your swords and
equip your Machine Dragons.
Descend, O royal dragon who inherits the blood of rulers.
Gambol in the heavens dressed in numberless lightings, Lindwurm!
So that's the Divine Raiment Machine Dragon of the girl said to be the school's strongest.
Yes.
But why is Lux using a Wyvern instead of Bahamut?
Among the girls of the squadron here, some still don't know about Bahamut.
He would like to keep it hidden as far as he can.
Also...
Also?
I think he still has a chance to win.
Where are you going in such a hurry,
Ms. Heiburg Republic Spy?
We have proof.
These are your secret messages for our neighbors of
the Heiburg Republic, detailing events at our school.
And the suspicious person showing up at school...
That was also your doing, wasn't it?
Apparently you set it up in order to frame Luxy.
We know everything.
Why not take off that mask and confess,
Saniya?
Looks like I don't have to
put up this front anymore.
Why are you doing this?
My mission is to kill you all,
undermining the new kingdom's military force!
This sound...
What is that?!
Is that really a Machine Dragon?!
It's time to put an end to these
boring spars and have a real battle,
you sheltered aristocrats!
Prepare yourself!
Your Machine Dragon is starting to go out of control. Surrender!
Recoil Burst!
Divine Gate!
What?!
Teleportation?
Starlight Zero!
What?!
Celis!
This is a state of emergency!
Start evacuating the island's civilians!
Yes, ma'am!
Philuffy?
Relie...
Don't worry. I won't let anyone take you.
Even if I have to stand against the new kingdom.
Are you all right?
This wound is nothing.
Could that be...
Yes. It's probably the Ragnarok that was supposed to be reviving soon.
Celis!
I'll take it down by myself.
It's my fault for allowing the enemy to come this close.
This is my responsibility!
No! Don't be reckless!
Divine Gate!
This is the end of you!
Celis!
I'd expect nothing less from my Celis.
You're still alive.
Saniya?!
But you can't possibly think it'll end like this.
Saniya! What are you doing?
Is that... Fugil?
It came back to life!
How can that be?!
It is regrettable, but you have to die, Celis!
Lux Arcadia!
You again?
You're a fool, handyman prince!
I bet you don't even know anything.
Saniya! Don't!
The person responsible for
your grandfather's demise...
is the girl behind you!
Hey! Celis! Celis!
Stay strong, Celis!
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I couldn't bring myself to tell you.
About Mr. Wade, your grandfather.
When I was very young, by chance I overheard details
of the depravities in the empire's governance.
I told Mr. Wade what I'd heard and he officially reported it.
He was thrown in jail and died there.
And top it all off, all of his lineage
were banished from the imperial court.
But the last thing Mr. Wade told me
was that I did the right thing.
So I must fight for justice in his stead.
What I wanted was to
distance you from danger.
But I failed.
I was deceived and got you involved in this fight.
I'm sorry.
You must hate me.
No. I don't.
That black sword device!
That's the one Luno was carrying.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
You can scold me about it later.
Manifest, O violent dragon who
feasts on the flesh and blood of gods!
Sever the black clouds of heaven,
Bahamut!
A jet-black Divine Raiment Machine Dragon?
I don't hate you, Celis.
You're strong and kind.
A little awkward, but I like you.
So I'll protect you.
In place of my grandfather whom you hold in such high esteem.
So you came, Black Hero.
You too are going to—
Out of my way!
It makes no difference. It's already over.
You can't kill a regenerating Ragnarok by yourself!
Reload on Fire.
End Action.
It's one of my brother's special techniques.
He continuously sends commands into the Machine
Dragon before it finishes executing his previous one,
enabling him to execute an unlimited amount of consecutive attacks.
Unlimited?
It does end eventually.
But not when his attack is parried.
It's when Lux has seen
everything through to the end.
Give it up! You'll exhaust your
strength long before you—
The Ragnarok will exhaust its strength.
Surrender, Saniya.
Before this fight is over.
You actually think you can win me over?
You, the rich girl honor student who couldn't see
who I was and who can't tell right from wrong?!
Can you really stab me?
Farewell, Celis.
Well, I never expected you to kill that Ragnarok.
That's...
But maybe it would've been better
if you hadn't killed it.
Now you've really pissed me off, Black Hero.
Who are you?!
You're not Fugil!
Don't put me in the same
category as that guy.
Do you know him?
My name is Hayes.
I'm looking forward to this, fake prince.
The nightmare from five years ago
will soon return!
The nightmare from five years ago?
Have you forgotten what happened on this island back then?
There. You're as good as new.
This isn't okay.
Huh?
I thank you for forgiving me,
but I object to the Luno matter.
I'm really sorry.
You saw so many embarrassing sides of me.
It's unacceptable! Unfair! Cruel! Frustrating!
Um... Is there anything I can do
to make you feel better?
But what bothers me the most is that I was happy when you saved me.
Huh?
I've always strived to never need anyone's help.
I don't understand how men feel
or how to talk with them.
So teach me. Like your
grandfather once taught me.
That's what I'll ask of you.
You mean...
Yes. In the name of House Ralgris,
I hereby accept your enrollment in the academy and
your entry into the knight squadron, Lux Arcadia.
Thank you.
But you know, if you show them
how kind you actually are,
I'm sure everyone will find you sweet and come to love you!
Sweet?
That was the first time
a man has called me that.
The nightmare from five years ago...
It's no good. I can't remember.
What's happening?!
This is sooner than expected.
I thought it would take a bit longer.
What's that?
It's one of the ruins.
I'll now reveal the true purpose of this trip.
kusaki mo nemuru yoru no sumi de sekai no fushi de
In the nook of night where even trees sleep, in a cranny of the world
neiki ni sotto mimi wo tatete hitomi wo tojiru
I hear the breath of someone asleep nearby,
close my eyes, and prick up my ears
kubisuji ni futto atatakana inochi no tsubu ga
A warm seed of life near my neck
koko ni iru tte sakenderun da koe naki koe de
is screaming that it's there, in a voice without voice
umarekawaretara owarinaki you ni
If we can be reborn endlessly
kimi ga nodo wo itamenakute
Let's take such forms
sumu you na sugata ni narou
that we won't need to scream so hard to be heard
sashiatatte futari tabi doko made arukeru
Now we're traveling, the two of us. How far can we go?
ikeru toko made ikou hohaba awasete
Let's go as far as we can, matching each other's pace
tsukiatatte futari tabi koko made kureba
And when we finally get to the end of the path, the two of us
kigi ni natte tachitsukusou
Let's become trees and stay there
raise ni natte mo zutto koko de nemurou
Even in the next world, let's keep sleeping there
futari nemurou towa ni
The two of us, let's sleep for eternity